So you’re always in front of the stage?
Watching the production from the audience point of view.
Right?
Are you interrogating me right now?
Get your hands off her!
And once we have strong suspicion of who it is,
we need to lure our prey out of his hiding hole to get evidence.
That's not true.
No!
My kids look so good!
So where’s your date?
- Oh, we’re not going on a date, Tita! - Just in a café at the mall.
So sorry to keep you waiting, Lori.
Remind me again.
Why did you ask me to pretend to be your boyfriend?
- Draco? - Draco?
- Draco! - Are you okay?
Sophie, what happened?
- What's happening? - What's happening? Are you okay?
Hey!
Adriana! Wait, hold on!
- Someone call an ambulance! - He was eating donuts,
and then he collapsed to the floor.
Draco! Get up!
Draco!
- Wait, wait. - Help!
- Sophie, get away! - Draco!
What's happening?
He’s dead.
Adriana, calm down.
Stop!
Don’t touch anything!
This is now an active crime scene.
Are you okay?
I’m kind of used to scenes like this, Al.
Used to it?
What do you mean, “used to it”?
Loki and I are members of the school’s detective club.
That’s why I’m used to encountering things like this.
Detective club?
I didn’t know you’re into that sort of thing.
Even I didn’t expect I’d get involved, or end up liking this kind of club.
We didn't... We...
- Stop, stop. - We didn't...
And who said you could step onto the crime scene, kid?
Shadows
in the dark are crawling
Keeping watch and barring your way
As if the line could not be crossed
To every scream and every tremor
These walls remain the only witness
Every noise is etched in here
Like fire and ammunition for your memory
Heed the warnings
The threats poised to strike
For this world
is not what you imagined
Heed the warnings
Open up your eyes
For this world
is not what you imagined
Heed the warnings
Chief Tobias!
It’s been so long since we last saw each other.
How long has it been since we last solved our case together?
You’re Estrada’s kid.
We last crossed paths at a crime scene last year.
Looks like even now, even here, you’re still carrying your curse.
Looks like your boyfriend’s well-connected with the cops, huh?
Look, he’s not being kicked out of the crime scene.
They’re letting him investigate.
Does he have connections?
Even I don’t get why he’s so influential with the cops.
Maybe he has a high-ranking relative?
I really want to chat with you more, chief.
But there’s still a case that needs to be solved.
Chief, is it okay if I continue assisting with the investigation?
Of course.
We need your skills for cases like this.
Chief, I hope you don’t mind,
if my colleague would also help me in this case.
So you’ve got a partner again now?
She’s actually my girlfriend.
And like me, she’s very observant.
Her insights have helped me a lot in solving cases in school.
You can ask Chief Estrada.
Um...
Would you mind if I help out with your investigation?
Maybe I can help.
If not, it’s okay.
Very well, you've proven yourself to be sharp.
Would that be okay, chief?
We really don’t allow it if you’re not in law enforcement.
But since I owe your father a lot...
And I know you’re good at this…
Fine.
I’ll allow you.
You can count on us, chief.
Lorelei.
Thank you.
Judging by the smell of almond from his mouth,
the victim was poisoned with Potassium Cyanide.
Just from the smell, you concluded that’s the poison that killed him?
Loki's right.
The almond scent isn’t the only sign that Potassium Cyanide poisoned him.
Potassium Cyanide inhibits cellular respiration,
preventing tissues from using oxygen from the blood.
Anyone who ingests, it will show bluish lips.
Gosh, where do you get that kind of information?
As far as I remember, we didn’t have a toxicology subject in our courses.
You mean you don't read books that aren’t part of your curriculum?
There’s no problem with that.
Especially if you’re not interested in toxicology.
That’s just what I came across when I watched a documentary.
- Hi! How are you? - Hi! Hi, Draco!
- How are you? - Yeah, I'm fine.
I thought you weren’t coming.
- Was it super traffic? - Yeah, totally!
Can we just move to a different table?
- Let's just transfer. - Yeah, sure.
They’re the only ones who had access to the victim.
And one of them is the murderer.
Huh?
Why are we the ones you’re accusing?
Draco is our friend!
Of all people, we’d never do that to him!
Being his friend doesn’t mean
that you can’t devise an ingenious plan to kill him.
Remember...
Betrayal comes from your friends, not from your enemies.
Potassium Cyanide takes minutes before it can kill someone.
Since you were with the victim 30 minutes before he collapsed,
you three are the primary suspects.
There are so many people in this café, right?
Why are you accusing us?
Couldn’t it be the staff?
Exactly. Why us?
No.
- Highly unlikely. - No, it wasn't us
Of all the customers here, only Draco died.
Which means the attack was targeted at him.
The culprit couldn’t guarantee
the poisoned food or drink would reach the victim
if it had to go through the staff.
This would all be easier if someone just confessed.
Or someone might speak up if they knew anything.
Because until someone confesses, we won’t be done here.
And we’ll have to hold the three of you.
We didn't do any... We didn't do anything.
Are you really sure about your conclusion that one of them killed Draco?
Are you doubting my deduction skills?
It’s not like that.
It’s just that we’re making a serious accusation against them.
What if they’re actually innocent?
Then we’d just be adding to their trauma.
You have a point.
But I'm confident in my deduction.
It’s obvious.
You can smell it a mile away.
Sorry, Lori, but I agree with your boyfriend.
There are no other possible suspects but the three of them.
Now, the real question is,
which of the three did it?
And how do we make them confess?
The way it looks, we might have a hard time getting the culprit to confess.
So, is anyone ready to confess?
You know, we’re just wasting our time here.
None of us killed Draco.
The four of us were on good terms.
Draco treated us well,
that’s why we could never do that to him.
Why are you saying we killed him?
What motive would we even have?
The three of you liked him.
Right?
I don’t know the victim,
but I can clearly see it in your behavior
and how you treated him.
I can clearly see in your eyes how painful his loss is.
But if my hunch is right,
he was seeing each of you separately.
But he didn’t want anything serious with any of you.
But if we’re looking for a motive,
it’s probably connected to love.
Because it’s one of the strongest motivators
for committing something so heinous.
That’s such a shallow reason to kill someone!
It’s better that we start investigating
rather than wait for them to confess.
For now,
let’s have everything on their table checked
for traces of poison.
They’re working on it now.
Lorelei has a point.
Honestly, I’ve handled a lot of crimes of passion.
You’d be surprised what people can do in the name of love.
See?
So, who do you think did it?
If you were observing them earlier,
you would no doubt have a guess on who it might be.
Have you been observing them for a while now?
Like you sensed something bad was about to happen to them,
so they caught your attention?
No, no.
We were just being nosy earlier because we had nothing to do.
We just observed them.
But we heard some things from their conversation
that might help us find the truth.
So going back to the question,
who do you think did it?
- I think it’s-- - Wait!
It’d be better if we write down
each of our guesses.
Huh?
Perfect.
Why?
Each of us has a guess.
If we tell each other,
we might influence each other’s conclusions.
What do you think?
I don’t think it’s a good idea.
Cases like this aren’t a game.
You must be fun at parties.
Wow.
Okay, listen.
This isn’t just a game.
We’ll just see if one, two,
or all three of us got the right answer.
Alright.
We have to wait until the lab results are out.
Unfortunately, that might take some time.
I’m dying to know where they found the traces of poison.
Wait.
Didn’t you say we shouldn’t be influencing each other’s guesses?
Fine!
Excuse me, I need to think.
I just wanted some time to relax.
But why do we still have to solve a case even here?
Looks like even now, even here, you’re still carrying your curse.
Maybe Loki really is cursed,
that's why bad luck follows him everywhere.
You won’t gain anything by joining that.
Staying close to Loki will only bring you tragedy.
What if Maggie’s right?
What if I end up like Rhea?
- What if-- - Lorelei
What’s taking you so long?
Sorry. Here it is.
According to my team,
they found traces of Potassium Cyanide on the handle of the victim’s teacup.
And on the tissues he used.
So if Potassium Cyanide was traced on the teacup handle,
that means the poison wasn’t in what he drank.
It could’ve been in the donut he ate,
or in something else he touched on the table.
How about his friends?
That’s exactly what’s strange.
No traces on the plates, teacups, or even the tissues his friends used.
None at all?
It’s impossible for our lab to make a mistake.
All items on the table underwent testing, right?
Yes. We’re thorough with our methods.
We didn’t miss a thing.
- Chief, excuse me. - Yes?
Could you enumerate all the items that were tested?
Four leftover donuts, four teacups with black tea,
four plates, crumpled tissues, two sets of fork and knife.
- Excuse us for a while, chief. - Yeah. Go ahead. Get this.
Are we all thinking of the same thing?
There are missing items from those tested for poison traces.
We can use that to figure out who did this to Draco.
It seems that we all have a suspect in mind now.
Let’s see if we all got it correctly.
Should we show our answers?
Not yet.
I’m going to do a magic trick.
And this will reveal the real culprit.
He’s good.
His methods are unusual.
Is that what you liked about him?
What?
Don’t you ever stop, huh?
We already told you, the killer of Draco isn’t one of us!
Actually, we already have a suspect.
Before we reveal who she is,
we want you to do something for us.
What are we going to do with those donuts?
We already lost a friend and you still want us to eat donuts?
How insensitive of you!
With the chief’s permission,
I’m going to use a method
that will instantly make the culprit confess.
I see.
So that’s what he was going to do.
All I’m asking is something simple.
Eat your donuts then we’re done.
And how are you supposed to figure out who the killer is if we eat that donut?
It’s a magic trick.
You’ll find out once we’re done.
The process will go faster if you cooperate with him.
It's an easy task.
And those donuts aren’t poisoned.
So, eat up!
I said eat up.
Is there something wrong, miss?
Why aren’t you eating the donut in front of you?
With everything going on, I don’t think I can eat right now.
By eating your donuts,
the two of you have proven your innocence.
While you have shown guilt,
by not eating yours.
Looks like we have the same suspect.
Me too!
You didn’t eat the donut
because you were afraid that it was poisoned...
Right?
And that also explains why you used fork and knife
while eating your donut.
We were all together,
how could she have poisoned Draco’s food and drink?
We didn't even see her touch those.
We noticed something missing from the list of items tested.
Is there no creamer here?
Alright, I’ll go get the creamer.
Stacy volunteered to get creamer for Draco, right?
And since she was far from you,
none of you noticed Stacy had already transferred
the poison into the creamer sachet.
The moment your friend touched it, his death warrant had been signed.
Hey, smooth.
And to avoid the poison being detected on the fork and knife,
she wiped them with tissue
before the poison could fully take effect on Draco.
Draco?
Draco!
Hey! Draco!
- What happened? - He was eating donuts
- and then he collapsed to the floor. - What's happening?
If you’re looking for evidence,
why don’t we ask Stacy?
Let’s find the creamer sachets
and the tissues she used to wipe the fork and knife.
Is it okay if we check your bag?
No need!
Really, Stacy?
You really did it?
Yeah! It was me!
I'm the one who poisoned Draco.
When I was in the restroom before he arrived,
I already put Potassium Cyanide on my hands.
The creamer sachets, the tissues...
They're true. Everything they said is true.
Why did you do it, Stacy?
Because I couldn’t let him be with someone else!
Here! Right here in this café!
This is where I confessed everything to him!
Stacy!
- Hey! Draco! - Hi!
- Hi. - Hi.
Good thing you came.
Yeah. How are you?
I’m okay.
- You look beautiful! - Cool, huh?
So, why did you suddenly ask me out for tea?
Excuse me. Here’s your order, sir.
- Wow. Thank you. - Your favorite, right?
I made sure of it.
Thank you.
I noticed you’re not with Adriana and Sophie.
I just wanted it to be just the two of us.
And there’s something...
There's something I want to tell you.
Okay, go ahead. What is it?
Um...
Hey! What is it?
Draco, I love you...
I like you, Draco.
I really, really like you.
My feelings have gotten too strong.
Maybe it’s better if I just tell you.
Um...
Stacy, honestly,
I really appreciate you a lot.
And I just want to thank you for everything you’ve done for me.
But I think you already know that I can only offer you my friendship.
Ah...
- Okay. - Stacy, I'm sorry.
Why, Draco?
Don’t you love me too?
Can’t you love me too?
It’s not like that.
Is there someone else, Draco?
Do you like someone else?
What is it?
He didn’t answer my question.
Maybe he likes one of you.
Maybe that’s why he couldn’t reciprocate my feelings.
Are you serious? That’s why?
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
I can’t handle knowing that.
That’s why it’s better I did this now instead of losing him to someone else!
You’re wrong, Stacy.
I’ve already confessed my feelings to him before.
But that’s when I found out, you’re the one he really likes.
Huh?
- What? When was that? - Sophie.
The only reason Draco won’t confess
is he doesn’t want to ruin our friendship.
And you got it all wrong, Stacy.
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can and will be used against you in a court of law.
You have the right to have a competent and independent counsel.
If you cannot afford the services of counsel,
the government will provide one for you.
- No. No. - Do you understand your rights?
- Come on. Come on, ma'am. - Sophie! Adriana!
- Sophie. - We'll help you, okay?
Alright. Please come with us now.
That Loki is a remarkable man.
Not everyone that age can solve a case like this.
He sure is unique.
Imagine him acting like a detective every day.
That’s just how he is at school.
So...
how did you get him to agree to this setup?
Setup?
What do you mean "setup"?
You really think I wouldn’t figure that out?
When something bad happens,
a person’s first instinct
is always to check on the person they love.
But when the victim collapsed earlier...
- that was the first thing he checked. - Adriana, wait!
- Not once did he ask you - Draco! Help!
if you were okay during the investigation.
He treats you like a colleague, not a girlfriend.
You got me.
You didn’t have to put on a show, Lori.
Why did you do it?
Why did you even come here?
If you just wanted to check on me, you could’ve just called or video chatted.
You didn’t have to come all the way here.
I came here to tell you that if you want to go back to Manila, you can.
You don’t have to worry about "those people" anymore, Lori.
What do you mean?
Your dad did everything he could to get them expelled from St. Barths.
I know it’s a big adjustment getting used to this place and feeling at home here.
But if you decide you want to go back to Manila, you can.
There’s no more threat to you, Lori.
You’re safe.
I want to stay. Alright?
I’m doing okay here.
People are nice, and the food’s great.
The air is cleaner here than back home.
It’s okay.
Do you plan to stay here permanently?
Maybe someday, I’ll go back to Manila.
But not right now.
I'm sorry, Al.
Don’t be.
I expected that’s what you’d say.
But I just had to try.
I was hoping you'd change your mind.
But it's okay. I respect your decision.
And I hope you’re happy here
Thank you for understanding.
Look...
I still wanna have chat with you and your "boyfriend."
But I have to go back to Manila.
You know how bad the traffic is going back there.
Have a safe trip back.
Yeah.
I’m glad we got to see each other again.
Take care, okay?
You too.
I’ll be back here soon.
Loki!
I still wanna stay here but I have to go back to Manila.
You know I might get stuck in traffic on the way there.
Oh, you’re leaving.
Have a safe trip back.
And, please...
take good care of my friend for me.
He knows the truth that we’re just pretending.
Not surprised, though.
Pleased to meet you. I'm Alistair Ravena.
Loki Mendez.
You’re lucky you won Lori’s heart.
Do you mind?
He tried to check earlier
if there were any irregularities in my pulse.
Are you really Lorelei’s boyfriend?
He even checked if my pupils dilated
when he asked if I was really your boyfriend.
That’s a lie-detecting technique.
I realized it a bit too late.
Well, you do have an interesting friend.
So why did you want me to pretend to be your boyfriend?
You wanna make him jealous?
He’s not just a friend to you, he’s much more than that.
No, I wasn’t trying to make him jealous.
When we were still in Manila,
he’s always there to protect me and save me when I’m in danger.
I just wanted to let him know
that I don’t need him to save me anymore.
Because there’s someone else who can protect me now.
Sometimes, our feelings can get the best of us.
This particular case is a warning to guarding our hearts...
so we won’t do anything we'll regret in the end.
After all, as they say, "too much love can kill you."
But the absence of love?
Could it make one a killer?
No.
- Lori, come on. - No.
- Lori, come with us. - No.
Come with us.
Get away from me!
- Come on! - Get away from me!
Come here, Lori.
- Come with us. - Help!
Come with us.
Lori!
Lorelei! Lorelei! Lorelei!
Lorelei, it’s me.
It's me, it's me. It's me, Loki.
Lorelei...
are you okay?
I heard you screaming, so I came in.
It’s okay.
It’s me.
It’s me, Loki.
Don’t worry...
nightmares are just your brain running a simulation
with bad graphics.
Nothing to fear, it’s all code in your neural network.
Here.
Have some tea.
Don’t worry.
It’s basically a warm infusion of plant molecules
designed to calm your nervous system.
Thank you, Loki.
Girl, you’re all anyone’s talking about here at Clark U right now!
Really? Why?
Everyone’s heard about the cases you solved at the other university,
that student at the café who got poisoned.
I see.
Some students from Clark U were there, they saw the incident.
Well, that explains it.
That explains why people I pass by keep staring at me.
Lori! Congratulations!
I heard you did an amazing job with that case
about the student who got poisoned at the café?
But I’m pretty sure that Loki did all the work!
The weather’s nice.
Anyway, I’ll see you at the Q.E.D. club room.
I already quit Clark Repertory.
It’s because I’m not comfortable anymore after what happened.
He even asked me to go to the club room later--
Wait, Loki accepted you into Q.E.D.?
Yes.
He said I’d be a big help to the club because of my photographic memory.
Oh, I’ll go ahead.
My class will start in a few minutes.
See you!
That’s so unfair!
Why did she get in and not me?
Don’t blame me!
I mean, I’m not the club's president.
Come on!
Come on! Our class will start in a few minutes.
It’s an improvement, huh?
De Los Santos...
Pass it, please.
Ms. Rios, congratulations!
You got the highest score in our exam.
Alright, class.
Next time, do better on the exam. Try to be like Ms. Rios.
Cool. That's so good!
How can they do that?
Right? How can they do that?
I just heard them playing. I thought it's chess.
Bro, check this out. That’s insane!
- How can they do that? - Solid!
Think about it, how?
Excuse me, coming through.
- So good. - Rook to C1.
Pawn to E5.
Pawn to C4.
Knight to F3.
Pawn to D5.
Knight to C3.
What are you guys doing? Why do you look so serious?
We’re playing game of Kings.
Chess, in layman’s term.
Chess? How are you playing without a chessboard?
The chessboard is in our minds.
That’s what we call blindfold chess.
No clients have come in yet, so we decided to play.
I also wanna test her photographic memory.
I want to see if she still remembers
where our imaginary pieces are on the chessboard.
And we’ve got a bet on this game.
If I win, we’re having lunch later.
So, I can’t afford to lose.
Right, Loki?
No…
I prefer to have my lunch alone.
Bishop to E7.
Oops, sorry!
Hello! Jamie speaking.
Really, ma’am?
I almost forgot. Okay, okay. See you.
Sorry, but we have to postpone the game.
I’m being called to the faculty room.
Let’s just continue our game later, Loki.
Don’t forget what we talked about, okay?
Don’t forget.
See you later, Lorelei.
We’ll see each other later.
Don’t try anything on Loki, alright?
Bye, Loki!
Are you and Jamie okay?
Of course. We’re okay.
I don’t think so.
You seemed visibly uncomfortable.
When she gave you a cheek-to-cheek,
you looked so shocked.
There's a palpable tension between you two.
No.
I’m just not used to Jamie yet.
- Anyway, I’ll go ahead. - Okay.
I’ve got you some coffee to wake you up.
Loki, maybe you could help me clean up?
Just maybe.
I can’t hear you.
I said, can you help me clean up?
So, are you going to help me clean up?
I’m always the one doing this.
Hello?
- Loki. - What? I can’t hear you!
I said, I’m always the one cleaning here,
so maybe you could help me out, right?
I even take out the trash myself.
Loki, you're disgusting!
You’re still that upset about Jamie, huh?
Is it because I allowed her to be part of the club?
You know, it’s your right as club president,
so I don’t really care.
Look, Jamie would be a valuable addition to the club.
She won’t be a burden, so I let her join.
Is that really the reason?
Or is it because she looks like Rhea?
So, you’re admitting that you’re upset with Jamie?
It’s not that I don’t like Jamie,
but there’s something off about her.
Because when we were investigating--
You’re a detective, right?
If you can do imaginary chess,
you should figure this out.
I still have something to work on,
so I won’t have time to delve into your business with her.
I thought you didn’t have any clients earlier.
No, it’s a personal request to me.
And I can’t involve our club.
I have to handle it by myself.
Jamie?
Where’s Loki?
Lorelei…
Loki…
Hey, you there!
Why don’t we play a game?
Can’t find him anywhere?
Oh, what a shame!
I will give you time.
Is 45 minutes fine?
Better hurry up 'cause his life is on the line!
Why?
What’s going on?
I apologize, in case, my actions offended you.
I was looking forward to spending that afternoon with him.
Why did it have to be him? Why not you?
I get you, girl.
It’s really hard being caught in the middle of your emotions.
You don’t even know which one to fully give in to.
Jamie, what if they find Loki but it’s already too late?
May I speak to Chief Estrada?
Sorry, the chief isn’t here right now.
He has a meeting with the president.
Please, can you call him? This is an emergency.
If you remember it, then write it down on paper.
Please, we're running out of time.
Don't you get it, Lorelei?
We’ll just waste more time,
if we keep trying to crack a code that’s not even our expertise.
You’re the only one we can think of turning to.
Can you crack that code?
It doesn't make sense.
Maybe we just used the wrong cipher.
Jamie, this is your opportunity to use your photographic memory.
Stop--
MkvDrama.net